早安
我要一杯咖啡
謝謝
Grazie.
（意語）你好
Ciao.
我叫薩佛，你呢？
我常在這裡看到你
我在提麥歐工作
那又怎樣，我沒興趣
每天早上都一樣
總會有男人問我名字
盯著我的胸部看
我只想安安靜靜喝咖啡
－可以嗎？　－你喝吧
- Grazie.
- Prego.
－謝謝
－不客氣
- Grazie, Walter. Buona giornata.
- Ciao.
（意語）謝謝你，華特
（意語）再見
借過
- Prego.
- Permesso.
Scusi.
- Hey.
- Hey. How was it?
慢跑怎麼樣？
Yeah, good. I got like...
20,000 steps.
很棒，我跑了兩萬步
是嗎，真不錯
Yeah? Nice.
你竟然醒了
I'm surprised you're awake.
Well,
I know you always get horny
我知道你跑完步會慾火焚身‥
after your run so I... Uh...
I'm gonna be so good today.
And friendly...
我今天會拿出友善的一面
Why?
怎麼說？
Because you've been accusing me
of being a bitch.
因為你說我很難搞
- I never once said bitch.
- Okay.
我沒說過這種話
不管怎麼樣，我不會找麻煩
Well, whatever,
I'm not gonna be that.
He's your bestie from college,
他是你在大學的死黨
and you want his approval
for some reason...
－你想得到他的認可‥
－我才不想
- I do not want his approval.
- Which is totally normal
這很正常，人都是這樣
and fine and human,
but I'm gonna be so fun.
我會很好相處
I'm gonna be the life
of the party from now on.
從現在起，我會成為
派對的靈魂人物
Well, don't overdo it.
They'll know it's fake.
別做得太超過
否則他們會知道你在假裝
我很喜歡他們，他們是好朋友
I love them. What?
They're our good friends.
放過我吧
Oh, my God.
－怎麼了？
－你嚇到我了
What? You don't think
I can be lovely?
我不能甜美一點嗎？
等著瞧吧
Just watch.
Okay, that's for you guys.
Thank you. Thank you.
這些錢給你們，謝謝‥
很抱歉這麼無禮，但你們得走了
I'm sorry to be so pushy.
I just really need you guys
to leave.
好
- Oh. Yeah.
- Uh. See you.
－再見了
－再見
- Bye.
- See you later.
- Yeah.
－晚點見了
－好
三千
真的嗎？
Mm-hmm.
早安
Good morning.
Morning.
Mm-mm.
Oh! There they are.
他們在那裡
Probably. Yeah.
Morning.
－早安
－你們好
Hi.
- Good morning.
- How'd you sleep?
－你們睡得好嗎？
－睡得很好
- Good. Yeah.
- Great.
Did you guys see the sky
this morning?
今天早上的天空好美
你們看到了嗎？
It was so gorgeous.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. It was.
－看到了
－對啊
真的很美
I love that top. So cute.
－我喜歡你的上衣，很可愛
－謝謝
Oh, thanks.
You know, I've never seen you
我第一次看到你綁頭巾，很漂亮
in a headband. It's so pretty.
Oh. Thanks. It's...
It's my new Italian style.
謝了
這是我新的意大利風格
I really like it.
我很喜歡
Let's get some food.
I woke up starving.
去拿食物吧
我一醒來就好餓
- Hmm.
- God. Do you guys want anything?
天啊
你們需要什麼嗎？
- No, I'm... I'm good.
- Yeah.
－沒關係，不用
－我也不用，謝謝
- I'm good. Thank you. Yeah.
- Okay.
好，老公，我們一起去吧
Babe, want to come
to the buffet?
好啊
Sure. Yeah.
Do you mind if I...
可以坐這裡嗎？
可以啊，請坐
No. Please.
That was fun last night.
－昨晚真好玩
－是啊
Yeah.
Um, I did want to come in
and keep hanging out.
我昨晚是想進房跟你繼續聊的
Just so you know.
Then you should've come in.
那你就應該進來
I just don't want to ever
make anyone feel,
我只是不想讓對方覺得‥
you know, uncomfortable.
不舒服
I don't think
that you're the type of guy
你不是會在那方面
讓人感到不舒服的男生
that could ever make
someone feel uncomfortable
in that way, you know?
You could probably go
a little bit
或許你該往另一個方向靠近一點
in the other direction,
actually.
Like... more aggressive?
你是說‥我應該霸道一點嗎？
I can't keep stuffing my face
at these breakfasts.
早餐讓我的嘴巴停不下來
But they're free, you know?
但又不用錢，真是太令人苦惱了
It's such a conundrum.
Morning. How you doing?
早安，你好嗎？
Who were the girls?
那兩個女孩是誰？
什麼女孩？
What girls?
我看到兩個女孩
從你的房間走出來
The two girls I saw
coming out of your room.
可能是房務員吧
Maybe the maids?
They didn't look like maids.
They looked like...
她們不像房務員
比較像‥妓女
prostitutes.
Oh, well, I don't know
what you're talking about.
我不知道你在說什麼
Listen, whatever you do,
聽著
你要怎樣都行
就是別告訴阿爾比
please don't say anything
about any of this to Albie.
Okay? Dad, please?
爸，算我拜託你
Look at those cannolis.
你看，有奶油煎餅卷
I've gotta find another job.
我得找別的工作
I'm just at a weird place,
you know?
我現在處於很奇怪的狀態
I've been...
我‥
I've been feeling so depressed
at home,
我在家好憂鬱
and I just thought I'd come here
我以為到這裡能有不同的感受
and feel something...
Is everything boring?
人生是不是一切都很無趣？
Boring?
無趣？
No.
當然不是
我只是覺得以前的世界一定不只這樣
I just feel like there
must have been a time
when the world had more.
You know? Like... mystery
or... or something,
有未解的謎團，或者別的
and now you come somewhere
like this and it's beautiful
反觀現代人到這個美麗的地方
and you take a picture,
and then you realize
拍了照片
結果發現大家都在
同一個地方拍了同一張照片
that everybody's taken
that exact same picture
from that exact same spot.
你只是在愚蠢的社群媒體
製造了多餘的內容
You just made some
redundant content
for stupid Instagram.
- Yeah.
- And you can't even
現在連迷路都沒辦法了
因為可以用地圖定位
get lost anymore 'cause you can
just find yourself
on Google Maps.
Throw away your phone.
那把手機丟掉吧
Yeah...
是嗎？
Throw it in the ocean.
丟到大海裡
God, it is so nice out today.
What do you guys wanna do?
今天天氣太好了
你們想做什麼？
Well, I've been bugging Cam
to go to Noto.
我一直要小卡帶我去諾托
那是個漂亮的巴洛克小鎮
車程兩個小時
It's this beautiful baroque town
like two hours from here.
There's these amazing palazzos
and artisanal shops.
有很壯觀的宮殿和手工藝店
Mm! That sounds cool.
－感覺很有趣
－聽到沒有？
See!
Harper thinks it sounds cool.
哈珀覺得很有趣
Honey, come on.
老婆，我都說我和伊森
約好要騎水上摩托車了
I already said I booked jet skis
for me and E.
Yeah, do it tomorrow.
明天再騎
老婆，我今天就想騎
Babe, I wanna jet ski.
And I don't know if we're
gonna get this weather again.
不知道明天天氣會不會這麼好
我們可以改天再去諾托
We can go to Noto any other day.
Cam, it's the one thing I said
I really wanted to do here.
小卡，這是我唯一想去的行程
我想去買聖誕節禮物
I wanna get Christmas presents!
拜託，現在才七月，小達
Jesus Christ!
It's July, Daph.
Christmas shopping.
這麼早買聖誕節禮物？
You know what,
that's actually fine.
好吧，沒關係
你們去騎水上摩托車
You guys
should do your jet skiing.
I'm just gonna go
to Noto by myself.
－我自己去諾托就好了
－不行‥
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
－別這樣
－親愛的，真的沒關係
Babe, it's fine. Honestly.
Unless you want to come?
還是說你想跟我去？
Mm?
Oh.
I mean, you don't have to.
不想也沒關係
You guys will have fun.
你們一定會玩得很開心
Yeah, right?
Harper, you should go.
是啊
哈珀，你應該去
Oh, yeah. Sure.
當然好‥
- Okay.
- Yeah, I'd love to go.
－太好了
－我很樂意
大家都跟我說諾托非去不可
I mean, everybody says,
"You gotta go to Noto."
Oh, God, yeah.
Gotta go to Noto.
沒錯
－諾托非去不可
－那太好了
Great.
Take pictures.
要拍照喔
- I made a plan for us today.
- I planned a tour.
我今天為我們規劃了一個行程
You planned a tour?
規劃行程？
Well, I couldn't sleep
last night.
我昨晚睡不著
For some reason,
there was a lot of noise
不知道為何，隔壁傳來很多噪音
coming through the walls.
Anyway,
they have a bunch of movies
總之，房間的電視
有很多電影可以租看
you can rent on the TV.
One of them was The Godfather.
You've seen it, right?
＂教父＂是其中一部
你看過吧？
- Some of it, I think. Yeah.
- "Some of it?"
看過一部分吧
一部分？
法蘭西斯柯波拉共拍了三部
Francis Ford Coppola
made three of them.
First two are classics,
前兩部是經典之作
and they were shot
right around here.
而且是在這附近拍攝的
So, I got us a car and driver
and we're gonna do
我請了一個司機
帶我們參觀電影中所有場景
a tour of all the locations.
You should come.
你應該一起來
來吧，吸收點新知
Come on now, educate yourself.
That's okay. I don't...
不用了
－我‥
－你應該來
Yeah, you gotta come.
It's okay, I... I don't...
－沒關係的，我‥
－你一定要來
No. You're coming. She's coming.
她會來
I'm being more aggressive.
這是我霸道的樣子
Oh.
But I feel like
that if you really loved me...
我覺得如果你真的愛我就不會走
you wouldn't leave.
I have to.
我不得不走
Is it the prenup?
Is that why you wanna...
是因為我要你簽婚前協議嗎？
Is it 'cause I had the prenu...
I could get rid of the prenup.
我可以撤除婚前協議
We can talk about that
when I get back. In two days.
我兩天後回來再來談這個
See? You always look
annoyed with me.
你看，你總是對我不耐煩
就是這個表情
You look like that.
譚雅
Tanya... you've done
a lot for me, okay?
你為我做了很多，幫我找醫生
You found those doctors.
I... I'm gonna live
because of you.
多虧有你，我才能繼續活下去
But ever since you
found out that you're gonna
但自從你得知可以多活幾年之後
have a lot more years,
I feel like you just realized
我感覺你好像覺得
自己被我困住了
that you were gonna be
stuck living them with me.
Couples don't always get along.
夫妻不一定永遠相處融洽
You knew I wasn't great at this.
I've been married four times.
你也知道我不太會當人夫
我可是結過四次婚
四次？
Four?
譚雅
Tanya?
I thought it was only three.
我以為只有三次
Tanya. Four, including you.
譚雅，四次是包括你
I just love you.
我只是很愛你
Tanya. Tanya, please.
You're gonna wet your dress.
譚雅‥別哭了
你會把洋裝弄濕的
買這件洋裝吧
我用我那一半買給你
你那一半？
我分不到一半嗎？
你昏了過去，根本沒跟他上床
我是願意跟他上床的
俗話不是說花錢才賺得了錢嗎？
小姐，不好意思
我朋友想試穿那件洋裝
Grazie.
－謝謝　－天啊，好美
麻煩動作快一點
我們還要逛其他店
（意語）謝謝‥
- Grazie.
（意語）非常感謝
Grazie, mila grazie.
Chi prendi in giro?
I'm gonna miss you.
- God. Be mature.
- All right.
- You guys will have fun.
I'm Daphne. Grazie for driving.
Here you go, sweetheart.
Thanks, babe.
Thank you so much
for coming with me.
謝謝你跟我一起來
Yeah, of course. I'm excited.
－不客氣，我很期待
－我也是
Me too.
再見，祝你們玩得愉快
Bye, guys. Have fun!
－再見，老婆
－再見
- Bye, babe.
- Bye.
Have the most fun ever.
－玩開心一點
－再見
Ciao.
So exciting.
好期待啊
Yay!
Dude, how awesome is this?
兄弟，很棒吧？
- Ciao, ladies.
- Hey.
你們好
This is where Michael Corleone
was hiding out.
這裡是麥可科里昂的藏身處
Another mafia family
was trying to kill him.
當時另一個黑幫成員想殺他
And his wife blew up over there.
他老婆就是在那裡被炸死的
The car was rigged
with a bomb meant for Michael.
車上有炸彈，麥可才是目標
But his wife is gonna drive
for some reason.
但那天不知為何是他老婆開車
Michele? Michele, andiamo!
（意語）麥可‥走了
走啦，你答應過的
Pacino realizes, he screams...
－帕西諾驚覺，於是大叫‥
－不要
No!
＂艾波洛妮亞＂
"Apollonia!"
It's too late.
Car explodes, she blows up.
但太遲了
汽車爆炸，她被炸成碎片
It's a great scene.
很棒的一幕
- She blows up?
- Uh-huh.
她被炸死？
真的爆炸？
- Like, blows up?
- Mm-hmm.
It's a little tasteless maybe.
那是不是有點沒品味？
Well, look, they're trying
to make a buck.
他們也只是想賺錢
最偉大美國電影的場景
正好是他們的房子
They own a house where they shot
the best American movie
ever made.
No, it's not.
才不是最偉大的電影
No? Why not? I think so.
為什麼不是？
我覺得是啊
Well, yeah, I mean, you would.
你當然這麼覺得
All right,
what's that supposed to mean?
這話是什麼意思？
It's because you're nostalgic
for the solid days
你懷念父權盛行的日子
of the patriarchy.
＂教父＂的確是好電影啊
They're undeniably great movies.
Men love The Godfather
because they feel emasculated
男人喜歡＂教父＂是因為
他們覺得被現代社會閹割了
by modern society.
It's a fantasy about a time
when they could go out
他們幻想回到過去
可以用暴力解決問題的年代
and solve all their problems
with violence...
Un focu d'amuri...
＂（意語）炙熱的愛啊＂
跟所有女人上床
and sleep with every woman...
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
And then come home to their wife
回家後老婆也不會過問
只會乖乖為他們煮意大利麵
who doesn't ask them
any questions
- and makes them pasta.
- Hey, hey, hey.
這是很正常的男性幻想
It's a normal male fantasy.
No, movies like that socialize
men into having that fantasy.
是看了這樣的電影
男性才會產生這種幻想
Movies like that exist
because men already
會拍出這樣的電影
是因為男性天生就有這種幻想
do have that fantasy.
We're hard-wired.
－這是我們的天性
－都是睪固酮造成的
Mm. Comes with the testosterone.
No. Gender is a construct.
It's created.
不對，性別只是人造的概念
You spent all that money
on Stanford,
你花了那麼多錢讓他上史丹佛
結果只是讓他被洗腦
he comes back brainwashed.
兩天而已
Two days.
All right.
Airport, go. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
去機場
（意語）我說不行‥我不想回去
No, no.
（意語）我說不行就是不行
Buongiorno. How can I help you?
早安，有什麼需要幫忙的嗎？
I... Uh...
我‥
are there any psychics
in this town?
這個鎮上有靈媒嗎？
Uh...
Psychics? Sorry, I don't...
I don't understand.
靈媒？
對不起，我聽不懂
Like, you know, old-school,
you know, Gypsy,
就是那種傳統的吉普賽靈媒
like, psychic fortune teller
type of person?
會算命的那種？
Oh. Oh, you mean...
我懂了，有的‥
Oh.
We have a tarocchi.
陶爾米納這裡有個塔羅牌占卜家
Oh, yes. Um, a tarot card reader
here in Taormina. Yes.
Do you think they could make
a house call?
他們願意到府服務嗎？
Because, like, I... You know,
it really is...
這算是緊急狀況
It's kind of an emergency.
Mm. Is everything all right?
－你還好嗎？
－我會待在房間
I'm gonna be in my room.
羅可
Rocco.
找算命師的號碼給那個瘋婆子
Uh. Uh, this is my boss,
so, I have to... get it.
是我老闆，我接一下
我馬上回來
- Go on.
- I'll be back.
Hi?
Hi. Where are you?
你在哪裡？
Um...
I'm at lunch.
我在吃午餐
Well, you need to come back
to the room
你回房間來，因為葛瑞格走了
'cause Greg is gone.
＂走了＂是什麼意思？
Gone? What do you mean,
he's gone?
我需要你
I need you.
Okay. Um... Well, I'm...
I'm not at the hotel currently,
好
但我現在不在飯店
- so...
- I told you
我要你待在附近，快回來
to stay close by.
Come back here!
我老闆要我回去
所以我得回飯店了
Uh, my boss needs me to go back,
so, I have to go back
to the hotel. Sorry.
－對不起
－這樣啊
- Okay.
- Oh.
No. We'll take you back.
我們送你回去
No, it's, uh, fine.
I'll just get a taxi
沒關係，我自己
叫計程車或想辦法‥
- or figure it out...
- Well, the driver can take her,
司機可以載她回去
再回來載我們
- and come back and get us.
- Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Take the car.
And, um,
對‥坐我們的車吧
let's... let's meet up later.
我們晚點再見面
好，你們人真好，謝謝
Okay. That's very kind of you.
Thank you.
And thanks again
for an entertaining day.
謝謝你們，今天很開心
Uh...
祝你們玩得開心
Yeah. Okay, have fun.
Um... I can Venmo you
－我再把錢‥
－不用啦
- for just the...
- No!
- Come on.
- Sorry, again. Bye.
－真是抱歉，再見
－再見
Bye.
Great. Thanks, Dad.
真是謝了，爸
What? Her boss needed her.
怎麼了？
是她老闆要她回去
You think she just wanted
to get away from us?
你覺得她是找藉口離開？
Maybe.
有可能啊
You do have a knack
for repelling women.
畢竟你常讓女人退避三舍
Do we embarrass you, Albie?
你覺得我們很丟臉嗎，阿爾比？
沒這回事‥
No, it's just...
I don't think...
你不知道你說的話
別人聽了會作何感想
you realize
how you sound sometimes.
They used to respect the old.
以前的人很尊重長者
Now, we're just reminders
of an offensive past
現在我們只讓大家想起
他們想遺忘的醜惡過去
everybody wants to forget.
Hi! Thank you so much.
你好，真是謝謝你
Yeah, you have an amazing
terrace,
這裡有一個美麗的露台
where you can
have a glass of wine
可以在那裡喝
我們葡萄園產的紅酒
from our familiar vineyards.
And here is our dining room,
這裡是飯廳
where you'll
have your breakfast,
可以在這裡吃早餐
當然了，請把這裡當自己家
and obviously
please feel at home.
- Oh.
- And, uh, feel comfortable.
好好放鬆，有任何需要我們都在
And anything you need,
we are here for you.
- Thank you so much, Peppe.
- Okay.
感謝佩哥
- Ciao, Daphne.
- Ciao.
－再見，達芙妮
－再見
Oh, my God.
Are you gonna tell me
what's going on?
現在是什麼情況？
So, I was reading about Noto
我在《建築文摘》
讀到有關諾托的文章
in Architectural Digest, right?
Mm-hmm.
裡面有這棟宮殿的照片
我想說或許能來參觀
And there were pictures
of this palazzo.
So, I was like,
"Maybe we can get a tour."
So, I called them,
and they told me...
於是我打電話過來，他們說
"You can rent the whole place
我們今晚可以整個租下來
所以我就租了
out for the night."
So, I did.
We're staying the night?
－在這裡過夜？
－不是很難得嗎？
Don't you think we should?
I mean, I was gonna wait
and see if it was worth it,
本來想說到了
再看看值不值得
但我們人都來了
非過夜不可，對吧？
but now that we're here
it's like
we kinda have to, right?
- I don't have any stuff.
- Oh, don't worry about it.
我什麼都沒帶
別擔心，盥洗用具那些
我都多帶了一份
I packed extra everything.
Toothpaste... Whatever you need.
Oh, God, this is just beyond.
天啊，這裡超乎我的想像
I can't believe it.
Come out here!
我真是不敢相信
快過來
那應該是游泳池
你猜誰帶了多的泳衣？
I think that's a pool.
And guess who brought
an extra bathing suit?
Don't you feel
a little weird being here
丟下老公不會有點奇怪嗎？
without the guys?
No. They didn't want to come.
And don't you think
不會啊，他們又不想來
你不覺得做自己
想做的事更重要嗎？
it's better to just do
what you want,
even if it's by yourself?
I mean, Cameron does
what he wants all the time.
卡麥隆隨時都在做他想做的事
Why let them have all the fun?
憑什麼只有他們能找樂子？
Hmm.
Let's check out the bedrooms!
去看看臥房吧
- Cheers!
- Cheers, buddy.
－乾杯
－乾杯，兄弟
I gotta say it, man.
I'm so proud of you.
我得說，我好以你為榮
I mean, you...
你這次真的是轟出全壘打了
You fucking knocked it
out of the park, man.
- You did it.
- Thank you.
謝謝
I'm not surprised.
但我不意外
我一直都知道你會成就大事
I always knew you were gonna
do something great.
Took a little while, but...
－但我多花了一點時間
－拜託
Come on. You're 36.
Give me a break.
你才３６歲，少裝老了
Well, you've been raking it in
for years now.
像你賺大錢已經好幾年了
Just wish you'd given me
a heads-up, you know?
希望你當初先跟我說一聲
- What?
- I have to hear
－什麼？
－聽蓋瑞皮茲納說了
from Gary Pizzinat
that you sold your company
我才知道你賣公司賺大錢
當時就沒有操作空間了
for a shitload?
And by then, you know,
it was too late
for me to do anything with it.
Oh, you mean, like...
Dude, I couldn't say anything.
我懂了‥但我當時什麼都不能說
You could have hinted.
你可以給個暗示
It's also illegal.
暗示也是違法的
A little birdie in the ear.
That's it. Information, dude.
派一隻小鳥來跟我傳話
就這麼簡單，資訊很重要的
I mean, come on, guys like me,
that's... that's all we got.
我這行都是靠資訊過活
- I'm sorry. I wasn't...
- It's okay.
－對不起，我不知道‥
－沒關係
- You know, I just...
- Don't worry about it.
－你懂的‥
－別在意，下次記得就好
Next time.
But you need to invest some
of that with us. Okay?
但你得在我們這裡做一點投資
I don't know if you've heard,
不知道你有沒有聽說
但我能幫人賺錢
but I make people money, bro.
I know you do.
我知道
Well, then let me do what I do
for you.
那就讓我為你效力
I... I would...
I would love that, E.
我很樂意幫助你和哈珀
拜託你給我機會
I would love to help you
and Harper.
Please, let me.
Look, just come in
to the office. All right?
來我的辦公室一趟就好
等我們回國
你來見見我們的團隊
When we get back,
you meet the guys,
and then you just hang out.
That's it. No pressure.
我們輕鬆聊個天就好
好，聽起來不錯
All right. Sounds good.
- Sounds good?
- Yeah.
－不錯吧？
－是啊
I am so stoked for you, E.
我真是為你感到高興，伊森
I'm so happy.
謝了，小卡‥
Thanks, Cam. Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Cheers, baby. Mm.
乾杯
Hey, buddy, two more.
朋友，再來兩杯
Wow.
Oh, she's the real deal.
她不是冒牌貨
Hmm.
A real, authentic,
old-world gypsy.
貨真價實的舊世界吉普賽人
跟我要求的一模一樣
That's what I asked for.
I don't think you're supposed
to use that word.
現在不能用那個詞稱呼人家了
What? All right.
She's, uh...
什麼？
那她很老派正統
- She's a real old-school...
- Gypsy.
Ma'am?
女士？
Yes, would you like some water
or some soda?
你要來點水或汽水嗎？
I could make you and I
a highball.
我可以調兩杯調酒
好
All right.
Guys in Italy
wear their pants so tight.
意大利男人的褲子都穿得好緊
Yeah, 'cause they want
to show off
他們想炫耀自己的老二
their dicks.
Why didn't you just tell me
你怎麼不直接告訴我要過夜？
we were really gonna
spend the night?
I really want Cam to think
that we just had so much fun
我希望讓小卡覺得
我們玩得太開心，決定留下來
that we just wanted to stay.
He has really intense FOMO
and also abandonment issues.
他有很嚴重的
錯失恐懼和分離焦慮
So, it's just gonna be
really funny to tell him
他知道我們在豪華宮殿享受
一定會很有趣
we're living it up
at some sick palazzo.
So, you're like playing games
with him?
你喜歡跟他玩這種遊戲？
We both do it.
It's like hide and seek.
我們都會這樣玩
跟捉迷藏一樣
讓生活多點樂趣
Keeps things interesting.
Yeah, well Ethan and I,
我和伊森不會這樣
we... we don't really do that.
So, I'm... I'm probably gonna
have to call him
我可能要打電話告訴他
我們會在這裡過夜
and tell him
we're gonna stay here.
Can I call Cam first, please?
可以先讓我打給小卡嗎？
－當然可以
－好
- Okay. Sure.
- Okay.
Hey, babe!
How's Noto?
老婆，諾托好玩嗎？
Amazing.
太棒了
I think that we're probably
gonna spend the night.
我們可能會在這裡過夜
－什麼？
－對
- What?
- Yeah.
This incredible palazzo I found,
so, I booked it.
我發現一棟很棒的宮殿
就把它租了下來
- Wha...
- But we'll be back tomorrow.
－我們明天就會回去
－等‥
W... You're coming back tomorrow?
明天才回來？
- Yeah, but have fun, okay?
- What?
－對，你們要玩得開心喔
－什麼？
Listen, I think I have to go
'cause Harper's
我得掛了，哈珀還在泳池裡等我
waiting for me in the pool.
老婆，什麼泳池？
No, uh, honey, w... what pool?
What are you talk...
－什麼？
－宮殿的泳池啊
The pool in our palazzo.
- Oh, you would die.
- I'll send you pics.
你看到一定會愛死
我再傳照片給你
- Love you, honey. Bye!
- Uh...
愛你，老公，再見
Oh.
They're staying the night
in Noto. She booked a palazzo.
她們要在諾托過夜
她租了一棟宮殿
－是嗎？
－對啊
- She did?
- Yeah.
That's kind of weird.
－有點奇怪
－她老是這樣
She always pulls this shit, man.
Fucking punishing me.
故意懲罰我
But you know what that means?
但你知道這代表什麼嗎？
我們兩個‥
You and me,
we're gonna fucking party!
今晚可以狂歡了
Let's go jet skiing.
去騎水上摩托車吧
All right. Okay. I'm coming.
好，我來了
Okay. Well... now what?
好‥然後呢？
You ask a question
and then the cards will answer.
你問問題，牌會解答
好
Oh. Okay. Um... I wanna know,
我想知道，我的丈夫‥
uh, my husband, you know, Greg...
葛瑞格他有件事‥
Something is just...
Uh, do... C...
Could you just leave the room
你‥
你可以暫時離開嗎？
for a second?
You know,
hang out in the bathroom
去浴室待一下
for a little while.
沒問題
No problem. Yeah.
Um...
Oh. Yeah. I want,
um... Is...
對，我想‥
我想知道我們會不會成功
I want to know
if we're gonna make it.
I mean, I just want to know
if our marriage is gonna last.
我想知道我們的婚姻
能不能維持下去
The cards say your husband
is in love with someone else.
牌說你老公愛上其他人了
這張牌代表的是欺騙
所以他在欺騙你
This card means deceit.
He is being deceitful.
And this card is beauty.
這張牌代表美貌
他的人生中有個美人
There's someone beautiful
in his life.
Uh, couldn't that be me?
那不是指我嗎？
Not you.
不是你
Not me?
－不是我？
－絕對不是你
For sure, not you.
（意語）美女‥愚者，無意識‥
美女，魔鬼‥
Uh, yeah.
這也太多負能量了
This is very negative.
（意語）星星‥無意識與潛意識
I can't believe I paid for this.
'Cause this is just really...
我花錢請你來的耶
（意語）你會發瘋然後自殺
你太負面了
You are so negative!
（意語）這就是真相‥
不該是這樣的，你應該鼓勵我
It's not supposed
to be like this.
You're supposed to...
This is supposed to build me up.
Take your crappy things
and your horrible cards...
收起你的破爛東西
這些可怕的牌和你的爛煙灰缸
and your shitty little ashtray.
No, I didn't want this.
This is creepy.
－（意語）我抽到斷頭人‥
－不要了，太可怕‥
No, it's...
No. You gotta go. Get out!
你得走了
－離開
－（意語）我抽到愚者，很危險
Yeah, well, whatever...
－隨便你說，你只是個騙子
－（意語）我抽到愚者‥
You're a con artist
is what you are.
That wasn't good.
根本沒用，太負面了
Negative.
Okay, guys, we'll meet up
around 7:30 downstairs?
我們七點半在樓下碰面？
Yeah, that sounds good.
可以，但我想睡個覺
你們要打電話叫我起床
But somebody give me
a wakeup call.
- I'm gonna take a nap.
- Okay. I'll come grab you, Nono.
好，我會叫你的，爺爺
Hey, Albie.
阿爾比
Yeah?
什麼事？
Hey, um...
I feel like you have this wrong,
distorted impression of me.
我覺得你對我的看法
受到扭曲，是錯誤的
I have always supported women.
I have always promoted women.
我一直都支持女性
我經常提拔女性
我是女性主義者
I'm a feminist.
我並沒有娶小女人當老婆
I mean, I didn't marry
some subservient wife.
你母親是個聰明幹練的女人
Your mother is a brilliant,
amazing woman.
- Did you talk to her?
- We didn't talk about you, Dad.
－你跟她談過了嗎？
－我們沒有聊到你，爸
No, I don't want
to get you in the middle. Um...
我不希望你被夾在中間
You don't have to say
anything to her.
你不必跟她說什麼
但如果你要跟她說話
But if you did say something...
I'm hoping you'd tell her
我希望你能告訴她
我很想念她和卡拉
that I'm really, really,
really missing her
and Cara, and...
And that I feel...
我覺得‥
我覺得很愧疚
I feel really awful.
She listens to you.
她會聽你的話
這件事是你無法彌補的
Nothing is gonna fix this.
是這樣嗎？
No?
你必須改變，爸
You have to change, Dad.
你不能再做你一直沉溺的事
You have to stop doing
what you're doing
and actually change.
做出實質的改變
I know that. And I have changed.
And I am changing.
我知道，我也改變了
我正在改變
I can change.
我有能力改變
- Oh, yeah?
- Yes.
－是嗎？
－沒錯
I can be the man
she wants me to be, again.
我能再次成為她心目中的男人
I'll see you at dinner.
晚餐見了
再見
See you.
Did she leave?
她離開了嗎？
Tanya? What happened?
I thought I was...
譚雅？
發生了什麼事？
我還以為‥
I thought I was gonna
get a reading.
她也要幫我算命
No. You don't want her.
你不會想算的
She was very negative.
她太負面了
Oh.
I'm sorry to hear that.
我很遺憾
I think I'm gonna take a nap.
我想睡個午覺
Okay.
好
Bye.
再見
No, you can't go. You can't go.
You just...
你不能離開‥
Please just sit on the couch.
I just...
拜託你坐在沙發上
我買了新一期的浮華世界雜誌
I did get the new Vanity Fair.
你可以看雜誌
You can read it.
Hey, hey. Psp. Psp.
天啊，嫁給我吧
- Vey! Marry me!
- Oh! No, grazie!
不了，謝謝
Um... oh, there's a machine.
I'm gonna get cash out,
那裡有提款機
我去領錢，等我一下
I'll be right back.
Come on, there's a couple more
stores I wanna hit.
走吧，我還有幾家店想逛
Lots of horny dudes in Noto.
諾托還真多飢渴的男子
What are these?
這是什麼？
The man, this table,
bought these for you.
那桌的先生請你的
Oh!
That's sweet.
真好心
I'm gonna have an edible.
Do you want an edible?
我要來一點大麻食品，你要嗎？
Try having two kids under four.
They help me relax. Have one.
有兩個不到四歲的小孩
你就知道了，這能幫我放鬆
來一個吧
Okay, I just have be careful.
我得小心一點
The last time I did edibles,
I took way too many
我上次吃大麻食品時
不小心吃太多
and I ended up on the floor
in the fetal position.
最後用胎兒的姿勢躺在地上
I kept saying,
不斷重複說＂我是女人＂
- "I am a woman."
- What?
什麼？
為什麼啊？
Why?
我也不知道
I don't know.
I think I was just...
tripping out on being a woman.
我覺得自己是女人很奇怪
Don't you like being a woman?
你不喜歡當女人嗎？
I'm fine with it, usually.
我通常可以接受自己是女人
Mm. I do.
我很喜歡當女人
I'd hate to be a man, honestly.
老實說，我很不想當男人
It'd just be so lonely.
I mean, they're so competitive.
感覺太孤單了
他們的勝負欲好強
這樣有辦法當朋友嗎？
It's like, can they even
be friends with each other?
Cameron and I went on a safari
卡麥隆和我有次去狩獵旅行
and, um, on safari, you see
我們在途中看到象群
all these pods of elephants
and they're all, like,
在河中洗澡，一起玩耍
看了讓人感到很窩心
bathing in the river and playing
with each other
and it's so sweet.
But it's just the moms
and the babies.
但那裡只有母象和小象
Because when the boy elephants
get too big,
因為公象只要長大了
就會被逐出象群
they kick them out of the pod.
And then the bull elephant
has to, like,
接著公象一輩子
都必須獨自在叢林中遊蕩
wander through the jungle
by himself
for the rest of his life.
I feel sorry for men, you know.
我為男人感到難過
It's like...
they think they're out there
他們自以為在做重要的事
其實只是在孤獨地遊蕩
doing something
really important.
But really they're just
wandering alone.
Whoo!
（意語）謝謝
Grazie.
- Hello.
- Buonasera!
- Buonasera.
（意語）你好‥
Um, listen, uh,
I just wanted to tell you
聽著，我們今晚沒辦法見面了
that I don't think
I can meet up tonight.
為什麼？
- Why?
- Um,
I'm afraid my son's
gonna catch on,
我怕我兒子會發現
但更重要的是我得改過
but, really, I...
I need to change.
I really have to change, so,
我真的必須改變
所以我們這週沒辦法再見面了
I don't think I'm going
to be able to meet up
at all this week. I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry too because I thought
我好難過，我以為
我們整週都會在一起
we were spending
the week together.
我知道，但是我真的不行
I know. But I... I can't.
And I'm really sorry.
我很抱歉
My son's on his way down,
so, I gotta go.
我兒子要下來了
我得趕快離開，但聽著
But listen, I really,
really loved meeting you.
我很喜歡跟你相處
- You're a wonderful...
- Me, too.
－我也是
－你很有魅力，很美
Beautiful woman,
and it was really fun.
我跟你玩得很開心
And this is for the ladies,
please.
這是給她們的
- Thank you.
- Thank you too. Thank you.
－謝謝
－謝謝你‥
My two favorite people
in the world!
我最愛的兩個人
我還以為你走丟了
Thought we'd lost you.
我有事情去找門房
I had to handle something
with the concierge.
- Uh-huh.
- You hungry?
－你餓了嗎？
－快餓死了
I'm starving.
他取消了
－為什麼？　－我不知道
沒關係
這裡很多有錢人，會找到新客人的
Gentleman.
你還在？
對啊
怎麼不回家？
我還有事要做
Okay.
這樣啊
我覺得你工作太認真了
但是‥
我很欽佩你
謝謝
Grazie.
我喜歡你管理團隊的能力
特別是男人
你不讓任何人欺負你
我想變得跟你一樣
Vabbè... Grazie, Isabella.
（意語）謝謝你，伊莎貝拉
你也是很優秀的員工
Um...
你太常和羅可聊天了，但是‥
你表現得很好
－謝謝
－不客氣
Grazie.
Prego.
祝你今晚愉快
晚安
You're nobody til...
＂找到愛你的人之前
你什麼都不是＂
Somebody loves you
So find yourself
Somebody to love...
＂所以去找個人愛吧＂
米亞
Mia!
－你都不理我　－我在工作啊
我得快點找到今晚的對象
我去買酒
酒已經有了
酒永遠不嫌多
Buonasera.
（意語）你好
Now, that you're a big shot,
people must be
現在你發了
一定常有人勾搭你吧
slipping into your DMs
left and right.
沒有
No.
What good would it do me
if they were?
有的話又怎麼樣？
我都已經結婚了
I mean, I'm married.
Dude, everyone cheats, E.
老兄，所有人都會偷吃
才怪
No, they don't.
Come on!
拜託
－是真的嗎？
－當然
- They do?
- Yeah!
Of course, they fucking do.
那是當然，出軌是機會型的犯罪
It's a crime of opportunity.
Jesus! If they can.
只要有機會，大家都會出軌
So, how's your sex life?
你的性生活好嗎？
Um...
Sounds great.
聽起來真棒
我也不知道
I don't know. Uh...
It's hard, I guess,
我覺得很困難
畢竟我們這麼瞭解彼此
when you know everything
about each other
and you've seen each other
on the toilet and, you know...
還看過彼此上廁所的樣子‥
There you go, man. See?
We've only got one life.
這就對了
人生只有一次
But Harper and I are...
但哈珀和我‥
過度依賴彼此？
- Codependent?
- No.
不是
I don't lie to my wife.
我不跟老婆說謊的
Really?
真的嗎？
Oh, man.
Fuck, I didn't know that.
天啊，我真的不知道
That is so sweet!
太溫馨了吧
Oh, the world Will be the same
＂世界還是老樣子
你永遠無法改變＂
You'll never change it...
After this, I am going swimming.
You're nobody 'til
Somebody loves you...
You already met a guy here?
你在這裡認識男生了？
Kinda. Yeah, I did,
he's really smart
算是吧，沒錯，他‥
很聰明，上過史丹佛
and everything,
he went to Stanford.
他是那種‥
You know, one of those guys.
He's really nice. Like...
人很好‥
maybe a little too nice,
you know?
有點好過頭的男生
I wish he just, like,
got my heart rate up
真希望他能讓我的心跳更快一點
a little bit more or something.
Portia.
波蒂亞
Don't spend your life chasing
emotionally unavailable men.
別浪費人生追逐
無法表達情感的男人
否則你一輩子都會想要去撞牆
Or you'll spend your whole life
just banging your head
against a wall.
我身上有什麼東西嗎？
他們一直盯著我看
Is there something wrong
with the front of me?
These guys are staring.
I think they're just
smiling at you.
我覺得他們只是在對你微笑
＂當你逐漸衰老
黃金無法為你帶來幸福＂
That gold won't
Bring you happiness
But you've been brainwashed
into thinking that, man.
你被洗腦了
這種想法很中產階級
It's very bourgeois.
一夫一妻制是菁英創造
用以控制中產階級的制度
Dude, monogamy was an idea...
created by the elite
to control the middle class.
Meanwhile, all the priests
were fucking the altar boys
反觀牧師會性侵侍童
and the aristocrats were fucking
everything that moves.
貴族則是任何會動的東西都想幹
這是亙古不變的現象
Same now as it ever was.
And the most ambitious guys?
野心最大的人性慾最強
They're always the horniest.
Like you and me, baby.
就像你我，朋友
And of course,
women are attracted to that.
當然，女人會受這樣的人吸引
But then, if you don't make
但只要你不實現她們的夢想
她們就會折磨你
their dreams come true,
they make you suffer.
That's why it's safer
to stick with whores.
所以花錢嫖妓比較安全
Excuse me.
別這樣嘛
你也很有才華
不敢當
No.
你的聲音很美
－你真的這樣想？　－真的‥
我可以幫你
我認識能幫你的人
我可以介紹給你認識
真的？
真的
朋友就是要互相幫助
我們是朋友？
還是床伴？
你這麼美，很難只跟你當朋友
Hmm?
我會考慮
你考慮吧
下流的老變態
米亞‥
Mia, Mia!
我可能找到人了
- What are you doing?
- It's okay.
－你在幹嘛？
－沒事的
（意語）米亞，走吧
走
Buonasera!
就是那兩個女孩‥
Those were the two girls...
- Ciao! Ragazze!
- Hi! Buonasera.
－（意語）你們好
－你好
－你們好嗎？
－幸會
- Lovely to meet you.
- Ciao. How are you?
你知道的，就是她們啊
You know, the girls.
How are you guys.
How you guys doing?
你們今天過得好嗎？
Um, fine.
還行
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm Cameron,
this is my buddy Ethan.
我叫卡麥隆，這是我朋友伊森
－你好
－你們好‥
- Hi, hi, hello.
- Hi, Cameron.
- I am Lucia.
- Lucia.
－我叫露西亞
－露西亞‥
- Yes, and...
- Lucia.
- Yes, and she is Mia.
- Mia.
－她叫米亞
－米亞
- Mia.
- Hi, Mia.
Are you guys from here?
Are you on vacation, what?
你們是本地人嗎？
還是來度假的？
- Um, we're from Sicily.
- From Sicily?
－我們是西西里人
－西西里人？
Mm-hmm.
Just two gals
只是相約到飯店酒吧來玩嗎？
hanging out in a hotel bar, huh?
- Yeah.
- You guys having fun?
－你們玩得開心嗎？
－開心
You guys, uh, you guys party?
你們喜歡派對嗎？
Yes, yes!
喜歡‥
你們有派對用品嗎？
You got any, uh... party favors?
I have pills.
我有藥
You...
I have Viagra.
我有威而鋼
We don't need Viagra.
我們不需要威而鋼
No? Also, maybe Molly.
是嗎？
還有搖頭丸
Oh, my God.
天啊，真的？
你是天使下凡嗎？
Are you kidding me?
Are you an angel
sent from heaven?
No, but these
are expensive, guys.
但是這些藥很貴，你們得付錢
You will have to pay for it.
I got money, baby.
That's one thing I do got.
我有錢，親愛的
我唯一不缺的就是錢
- Let's fun!
－那就一起玩吧
－一起玩吧
This is the only snack
I could find.
我只找得到這個點心
Want some?
要來一點嗎？
You still high or what?
你的藥效還沒退嗎？
Hi.
你好
So...
所以‥
伊森有沒有變？
has Ethan changed at all?
No.
完全沒變‥
No, not at all.
He's exactly the same.
他還是同一個人
這是好事
That's good!
我看過很多男人，原本是‥
'Cause I've seen
a lot of guys who are, like...
Well, not nerds. I mean,
Ethan's not a nerd, but...
我不是要說書呆子
伊森不是書呆子‥
－他就是‥
－我的意思是‥
Yes, he is. He is!
I just mean, like,
他們從沒當過渣男
they were never players.
And then they make
all this money
但一夕間暴富讓他們變了
甚至開始偷吃
and they just start
acting different and, like,
cheating.
No. No,
Ethan would never do that.
伊森不可能偷吃的
他不是那種人
He's not like that. He's...
他老實過頭了
He's honest to a fault. He's...
他‥
God, I'm so glad that Cameron
has a friend like Ethan.
我很慶幸卡麥隆
有伊森這樣的朋友
Honestly, the guys
that Cameron works with...
說真的，跟卡麥隆工作的那些人
a very dark triad.
有很多人內心很黑暗
Like, for real.
真的，他們是一群神經病
- Psychopaths. I'm not kidding.
- Hmm.
我沒在開玩笑
但卡麥隆不是
But not Cameron.
No. Cameron's, like, naughty,
like a little boy is naughty.
沒錯，卡麥隆只是調皮
他跟小男孩一樣
其他人是像馬多夫那種禽獸
These other guys?
I mean, they're like
Bernie Madoff monsters.
They will fuck you up.
他們會把你搞死
And they're the most
successful guys in finance.
他們是金融圈最成功的人物
Oh, Jesus!
老天，太冷了吧
Oh, shit, this is cold.
I got sensitive nips.
我的乳頭很敏感
- Hey.
- Beer?
- Oh, thank you.
要啤酒嗎？
謝謝你
How was your day?
今天還好嗎？
Uh, pretty grim...
actually.
滿可怕的
- Hmm.
- I feel like if I
要是我殺了我老闆
說我是幫她安樂死也不為過
murdered my boss, I could
argue it was euthanasia.
Yeah.
Uh, what about you?
那你呢？
晚上過得如何？
How's your night?
Better now.
現在好多了
Oh.
Sorry. Um,
對不起
was... was I...
－我是不是‥
－不是
No, uh... No, no,
that was... it's fine.
沒事‥
I... I just wasn't expecting it,
you know?
我只是沒預料到
- Well, expect it.
- Okay.
－那我來囉
－好
Is everything okay?
你還好嗎？
Yeah! Yeah, everything's...
I'm just...
我沒事‥我只是‥
It's been a long day.
今天發生了很多事，我有點累了
And I'm just kinda fried,
I think.
- Mm. Yeah.
- Yeah.
－我想也是
－是啊
Do you wanna
go back to my room or...
你想到我房間嗎？
我想直接睡了
Yeah, no. I think
I just need to crash.
- If that's okay?
- Yeah, yeah. I think me too.
－可以嗎？
－好，我也一樣
- Sorry.
- N... no, it's fine. You...
對不起
－沒關係‥
－我們可以明天見面
I mean, we could
hang out tomorrow.
- Are you around tomorrow?
- Yes, absolutely.
－你明天會在嗎？
－當然
I would love that.
Um...
我很樂意
Do you want me
to walk you back to your room?
要我送你回房嗎？
- Um, sure.
- Great, okay.
好
- Oh, don't forget your beer.
- Oh, thanks. Sorry.
－別忘了你的啤酒
－謝了，抱歉
- You got your stuff?
- Yeah.
－東西都拿了嗎？
－拿了
Um, thanks for the beer.
謝謝你的啤酒
Yeah. No problem.
不客氣
I hope I didn't make you
feel weird.
- No. No, no.
- Yeah, yeah.
Don't... don't apologize.
Honestly.
- Daphne?
- Hmm?
達芙妮？
Do you think Cameron
ever cheats on you?
你覺得卡麥隆出軌過嗎？
Maybe just once.
可能只有一次吧
就我所知
That I know about.
不用可憐我
Don't feel bad for me.
我學會怎麼面對了
I figured out how to handle it.
Like today.
像今天這樣
I do what I want.
我做自己想做的事
所以我不會心懷怨恨
So, I'm not resentful.
你是怎麼面對的？
Yeah. How do you handle it?
I...
我‥
I'm not a victim.
我不是受害者
That's all I meant.
我是這個意思
快開門
Hey!
Open the door!
Come on!
你在裡面做什麼？
What are you doing in there,
man? Hello?
有人在嗎？
Open up, come on!
快開門啊，你這小男孩‥
Sweet little baby boy.
Come on, go see him.
你去找他
He's a little shy.
Go see shy boy.
他有點害羞，有什麼好害羞的？
Take care of him.
好好照顧他
Take care of her! Grazie!
What are you doing,
little shy boy?
Come on! Bring him over.
Hey, big boy.
No?
不要嗎？
Okay.
好
Hey, this is Ethan.
我是伊森
現在沒辦法接聽，請留訊息
Sorry I can't take your call.
Leave a message.
待續
謝謝觀賞